Kristopher Kohlmeier

Media Technologies

kristopherkohlmeier@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/kris-kohlmeier/ +1 (805)-276-4713 Camarillo, CA, 93010, United States

Early career media engineer with software development experience. Fast learner with a proven record of quick thinking and solution execution in live production environments. Experience with agile development patterns and delivering software in team environments.

Work Experience

Production Technology Assistant

Jun 2021 - Present

<u>Crossroads Church</u> | Camarillo

Operated part-time as the main point person in charge of A/V production equipment on a weekly basis. Supported volunteer teams as well as staff members with A/V related tasks and training.

- Planned and executed over \$40,000 in A/V installs and upgrade projects.
- Onboarded new stage lighting console for production volunteers, offering training, on-call support, and programming when needed.
- Utilized projection mapping to bring a unique look to the stage for holiday special events.
- Personally repaired out of warranty stage lights to preserve production budget.

Animation Technology Internship

Jun 2023 - Aug 2023

<u>Skydance Animation Studios</u> | Santa Monica

Three month long internship to work with and learn from five different technology departments in an animation studio.

- Audited studio codebase, leveraging Rez API with a python script for the pipeline engineers.
- Created SOP for and assisted in the integration of a studio-wide printer system.
- Created a tracking document for all editorial hardware during studio location moves.
- Solved Jira Tickets for the general IT help desk.

Projects

Story Development Software

Jan 2024 - May 2024

Prototype server and client that ingested storyboard panels and .EDL files to track editorial changes for a film in early production. Used as a senior project and developed in SQL and Python.

Padoq Nov 2024 - Present

Web application being developed with a small team as a joint venture to eventually bring to market. Current technology stack includes Vue, Ionic, and Firebase.

Core Skills

Projector systems, Broadcast cameras, Stage lighting, Live audio mixing, Small electronics repair, Dante, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Vue, Python, C, SQL

Education

California State University Channel Islands

Jan 2021 - Jun 2024

Bachelor of Science Computer Science GPA 3.4